Guide to the Jerome T. Barrett Collection, 1913-2010 LAC0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jerome T. Barrett Papers, 1937-2005; Record Group 2
  - Jerome T. Barrett Writings, 1960-2008; Record Group 2 Series 1
    - Unpublished Writings, 1960-2006; Series 1 Subseries 2
      - University of Wisconsin School for Workers-correspondence and public televsion scripts, 1996; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 205, Folder 15)
      - SPIDR Oral History-Maria Volpe correspondence, November 13, 1996; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 205, Folder 16)
      - IBN Case: IBB Briefing for Kellog Plant Management, October 14, 1997; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 205, Folder 17)
      - "Some thoughts for New Mediators on Mini Tools of Mediations"-Original draft and revisions, 1976-2000; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Labor-Management Computer Exercise- Notes, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Project Grants: Kentucky Oral History Commission, 1984-1986; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Funding Request: FMCS Proposals, 1984-1985; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Funding Requests: Harvard University, 1985-1987; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Project Grant: Hewlett Foundation and Northern Kentucky University, 1985-1987; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 6)
      - Funding Request: Upjohn Institute, 1985-1986; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 7)
      - Funding Request: Miscellanous Foundations Refusal Letters, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 8)
      - Taped Oral Histories: 34 interview notes and Chronology-Eastern Airlines [1], March 4-July 21,1986; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 9)
      - Taped Oral Histories: 34 interview notes and Chronology-Eastern Airlines [2], March 4-July 21,1986; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 209, Folder 10)
      - Mgt 210-"Experiences in Groups", 1954; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - "A Systems Approach to Instructional Design involving Preparation for a Safe and Effective Jogging Program", June 29, 1978; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 2)
      - "An Analysis of Group Behavior", 1979; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 4)
      - "Assessing the Labor Relations Performance and Training Needs of First Line Supervisors and Union Stewards", 1979; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 5)
      - "Phase 1 Reading requirement on Training Needs Assessment", April 2,1979; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 6)
      - "Airport 1979: Observations of Airport Services and Group Process", August 15, 1979; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 7)
      - DOL/Consulting Project in Thailand: A Description and Discussion, 1980; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 8)
      - "A Modest Proposal for Usiong Labor-Management Committees in K-12 School Systems", 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 9)
      - Annotated Bibliography: "Organizational Development" and "A Systems View", 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 10)
      - "An Evaluation for a Train-the-Trainers Workshop", 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 11)
      - "Trust Level (TORI) and Adult Learning", 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 12)
      - "Three Short Papers on Conflicts", February, 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 13)
      - "Organization to Larger System Conflict Management", April 14, 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 14)
      - "Video Training Methods and Techniques", 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 15)
      - "HRD Strategies and the Experienced Professorial Employee", 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 16)
      - "Good Teaching Versus Professorial Research: An Essay", 1981; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 17)
      - "Exper-SIM", March 30, 1982; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 18)
      - "A Research Proposal on Joint and Seperate Training at the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service", 1982; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 19)
      - "Conclusions to Learning Contract on HRD/OD Interaction within an Organization", 1982; Record Group 2 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 246, Folder 20)
  - Dissertation Research, 1968-1992; Record Group 2 Series 2
    This series is arranged by research document type.
    This series consists of research notes, drafts and correspondence pertaining to Jerome T. Barrett's doctoral dissertation.
    - Rolodex/Index card Planning Notes [1], undated; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Rolodex/Index card Planning Notes [2], undated; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Paul Tinning correspondence-Oregon State Conciliation Service, October 21, 1968; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Jamestown and Cumberland Labor-Management Committee Reports, 1975-1982; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Labor-Management Committee Pamphlets and Reports, 1979-1992; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Dissertation Planning, February 1981-June 1982; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Vernon G. Talbot Research and Correspondence-Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, February 1981-June 1982; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Dissertation Notes, Work Plan, & Schedule, 1981-1982; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Research Materials: Microfilm, 1981-1982; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Drafts: Dissertation Proposal, July 13,1982-March 2, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - George Washington University Course Schedule, Summer 1982; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Miscellanous Correspondence, 1982-1984; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Dissertation Abstract-IRRA Correspondence & San Francisco Roundtable, July 25, 1983-January 1984; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Delphi Materials-Notes & Correspondence, June 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Draft edits and correspondence, June 11-July 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Dissertation Research Planning & Notes, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - [1] Joint Labor-Management Training Questionaire Number 1, July 18-21, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - [2] Joint Labor-Management Training Questionaire Number 2, July 14-August 6, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - [3] Joint Labor-Management Training Questionaire Number 3, August 1, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - [4] Phone Interview Notes, August 16, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - [5] Questionaire Notes and Summary, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Draft Dissertation-Garland Dean Wiggs Edits and Comments, October 18,1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Dissertation: Pre-Defense Copy, December 13,1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Draft Dissertation, December 14,1983; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Notes & Correspondence-Dr. Garland Wiggs, 1983-1984; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Draft Dissertation Copy, March 21,1984; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Final Exam and Graduation Materials-George Washington University 163rd Commencement, April 9-May 6,1984; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Draft Dissertation: Pre-Defense Copy with Note, December 15, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 2 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Speeches and Presentations, 1967-2012; Record Group 2 Series 3
    This series consists of speeches and presentations delivered by Dr. Barrett to professional associations, universities and labor-management organizations.
    This series is arranged by individual speech or presentation.
    - Speech to the 24th Annual Convention of the Mississippi State Council of Carpenters, undated; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - January Month Conference of Business Administration-Carroll College, Waukesha, Wisconsin, 1967; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - National Center for Dispute Settlement-Resolving Impasses in Public Employment, November 15, 1969; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - "Brochures on Conferences Where J.T. Barrett Spoke", 1973-2000; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Report of the 1973 Joint Labor-Management Leadership Conference, 1973-1974; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - ALMA Speech and Conference Materials-Santa Fe, NM, July 7, 1973; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - "Legislative and Judicial Treatment of Public Employee Work Stoppages"-University of Minnesota, PERLA conference, December 7, 1973; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - ST. Louis Remarks-"What Mediators Should Know about the Pension Reform Law of 1974, with attached 2012 note, 1974-2012; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Miscellanous Outlines-Interns, New Mediator Orientations, ALMA, and "Minnesota Students", 1975-1977; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Association of Labor Mediation Agencies Remarks-Halifax, Nova Scotia, July 29, 1975; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - FMCS-University of Detroit Conference Remarks-"Changing Union Representation and Influence", June 1, 1977; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Industrial Relations Alumni Society-First Annual Institute Proceedings-"Hot Issues in Labor Relations", March 29-30. 1979; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Notes-Final Plenary Session, National Seminar, 1979; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - Notes-Cornell University Conference, July 24, 1980; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - Cincinnati IRRA-"A New Steward and Foreman Required in the 1980's", February 28, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - IRRA Annual San Francisco Meeting-agenda-Jerome Barrett Listing, December 30, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 16)
    - Miscellanous Speech Drafts & Notes, 1985-2011; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - Kentucky Labor Cabinet-Panel Notes and Correspondence, April-June, 1985; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - Keynote Remarks at Mercer County, PA Labor-Management Committee, October 10, 1985; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 19)
    - Notes for Atlantic City and Northern Kentucky University Conferences, May-September, 1987; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 20)
    - Crawford County Labor-Management Council, October 15-16, 1987; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 21)
    - Montana Arbitrations Association conference-Notes and Plenary Keynote session: "Blending the Three Tracks in Labor-Management Relations", April-May, 1989; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 22)
      This series consists of speeches and presentation delivered by Dr. Barrett at a variety of professional and scholarly venues.
    - Newsclipping: "105 attend Management, labor Session" from Decatur (IL) Area Labor-Management Committee, H&R, March 16, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 23)
    - "Notes for Remarks to Professor Mets"-University of Massachusetts, Boston, November 14, 1995; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 24)
    - Print-out: "Briefing on Win-Win Bargaining for the Airline Pilots at DHL Airways", 1995; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 25)
    - Panel Correspondence- Pacific Network for Dispute Resolution, September-October, 1996; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 26)
    - IRRA Luncheon-"The FMCS at Age 50", December 4, 1996; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 27)
    - Conference Notes, Certificate, and Correspondence: Sonoma County-"Innovations in Labor-Management Relations", October-December, 1997; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 28)
    - Notes and Correspondence-Georgia State University, Atlanta Chapter IRRA Panel, February 19-23, 1998; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 29)
    - Ohio State Employment Relations Board-Remarks, April 2, 2000; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 30)
    - "Learning from Historic Experience: the FMCS in the USA"-Iasi, Romania conference, October 29, 2001; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 31)
    - Buckeye Labor-Management conference, October 9, 2003; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 32)
    - Invitation: "Jerry Barret-Perspectives on the Field: Evolution of ADR" Book Seminar, September 29, 2007; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 33)
    - Fordham University Law School-Keynote Remarks & Correspondence, March 17, 2008; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 34)
    - Ohio State Journal on Dispute Resolution Symposium, 2009; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 35)
    - "Labor-Management Conflict Resolution and the Larger ADR Community", October 27, 2009; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 36)
    - "A Speech on the new Norma to Montgomery County and McGEO", November 29, 2011; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 186, Folder 37)
    - Department of Labor-Public Sector Speeches, December 1970-October 1976; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - 18th Annual Louisiana Public Personnel Management conference-"The Need for Positive Public in State and Local Government Labor Relations", December 10, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - University of Georgia: "Public Management and Organized Employees" Seminar Materials and Correspondence, March-June, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence from R.H Helmes, Xavier University, April, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - University of Oregon Law Center-"Public Policy Developments in Public Labor-Management Relations", May 21, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Association of Labor Mediation Agencies conferences-New York, California, and Colorado Remarks, 1971-1972; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - Partners in Change papers: "Jointly Confronting Change and Planning a Joint Future." Bureau of Labor Management Relations and Cooperative Programs-DOL, May, 1989; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - "Interest-based Problem Solving at Work Coursebook," by JT Barrett and John O'Dowd, June, 2004; Record Group 2 Series 3 (Box 195, Folder 20)
  - Professional Association Materials, 1970-2003; Record Group 2 Series 4
    This series consists of materials relating to Dr. Barrett's professional organization associations, mainly in reference to his membership in the Society of Professionals in Dispute Resolution (SPIDR).
    - SPIDR Election-Candidate Bios, undated; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - "How to Bargain in the Public Service" by Robert H. Hastings, AFL-CIO, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Jerome T. Barrett SPIDR Certificate, July, 1973; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Center for Labor and Human Resources-Temple University-"The Origins, Structure, and Operation of Areawide Labor-Management Committees" Report for the U.S. Department of Labor, June 1, 1977; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - SPIDR Occasional Paper 81-85, November 1981-February 1985; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - IRRA Newsletter, Volume XXIV, No.1-4; Volume XXV, No.1-3 (Industrial Relations Research Association Series), February 1982-September 1983; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Flyer-"Cape Cod conference", American Arbitration Association Boston Regional Office, May 27, 1982; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Reprint: Thomas Colosi, SPIDR President, in "Government Employee Relations Report, No.985", October 25, 1982; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - IRRA conference-fee deposit & letter, February, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - NIDR Dispute Resolution Forum-"SPIDR's Ethical Standards of Professional Conduct"/NIDR News, December 1983-August 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - SPIDR Washington D.C. Chapter-Board of Directors Minutes, Bylaws, and Treasurer's Reports, May 23, 1984-July 12, 1989; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - SPIDR Pamphlets-Miscellanous, 1986-1992; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - SPIDR Directory-"Dispute Resolution and Training Programs", October 1987; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - Thomas J. Manley and John R. Stepp booklet-"Innovations in Sunbelt Collective Bargaining", 1987; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 14)
    - SPIDR Oral History Planning-Notes and Correspondence, 1988-1999; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 187, Folder 15)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, September 1983; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, September 30, 1987; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, 1988; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, December 1990; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, 1992-1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - New SPIDR Member Acceptance Letters/Roster, April 26, 1993-July 26, 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - New SPIDR Members List, November 1, 1993-October 1, 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, 1995-1996; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - SPIDR 25th Anniversary Membership Directory, 1997; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, 1999; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - SPIDR Membership Directory, 2000; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Meetings-Schedule and Report Packet-Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, October 8-11, 1992; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Meeting-Schedule and Report Packet-Toronto, Ontario, January 29-30, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Meeting-Schedule, Report Packet, Bylaws, and Correspondence-Washington D.C., May-June, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Meeting-Schedule and Report Packet-Toronto, Ontario, October 20-24, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Meeting-Agenda and Report Packet-Toronto, Ontario/San Antonio, October 1993-January 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Roster List, November 1993-April 1997; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Meeting-Schedule and Report Packet-Washington D.C., January 25-June 12, 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - SPIDR Board of Directors Meeting-Schedule and Report Packet-Dallas, Texas, October 26-30, 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Interview of Rick Reilly, 12th President of SPIDR-Transcript and Disk, May 9, 1988; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - SPIDR Commission on Qualifications-Issues Paper, September, 1988; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - SPIDR Financial Statements & Audit Correspondence, March 1989-January 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - SPIDR Executive Committee conference call Minutes-Miscellanous, September 1, 1989-April 19, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Report of SPIDR Organization and Structure Committee, October 1989; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - SPIDR Washington Area News, November 1989-Spring 1998; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - SPIDR-William & Flora Hewlett Letter and Development Grant, 1989; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Peace in Action-Mediation articles, 1989-1991; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - SPIDR Greater Delaware Valley Chapter Mailings, March 1990-June 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Transcript: "Interview with Robert Helsby, First President of SPIDR" with attached disk and John Jay College leaflet, October 18, 1991-March 2, 1998; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - SPIDR LeaDRship Letter-newsletters, January 1992-August 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - SPIDR Pacific Northwest Chapter Bylaws, March, 1992; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - NAME, ILO, and ConflictNet pamphlets, 1993-1995; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - SPIDR-Associate Member Research Project, 1993-1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - SPIDR Memorandums-Miscellanous, 1993-2000; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - SPIDR History Interviews and Abner Award Correspondence materials, 1993-2003; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - SPIDR officer and Board of Director Elections-Candidate Biographical Information, 1993-1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - SPIDR Southwest Regional conference-"Ethics and Standards"/Campus Mediation High School and College" panelists-San Antonio, Texas- Part 1, August 14, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - SPIDR Southwest Regional conference-"Ethics and Standards"/Campus Mediation High School and College" panelists-San Antonio, Texas- Part 2, August 14, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Dianne Walker Letter to Board of Directors, December 7, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - Joint Committee on Standards of Conduct Memorandum, December 7, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 1-6, 1977-1982; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 7-8, March 1983-December 1984; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 9-12, January 1985-December 1988; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 13-15, 1989-1991; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 16-18, Winter 1992-Summer 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 19-21, Fall 1994-Spring 1997; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 22, Fall 1997-Fall 1998; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - SPIDR News Vol. 23-24, 1999-2000; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 27)
    - SPIDR staff consultation-Support Center of Washington D.C. report, 1992-1993; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Credentialing Process-San Diego Mediation Center, 1992; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - SPIDR Washington D.C. Chapter-Membership Directory and Mailings, 1992-1995; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County Public Schools-Student Mediation Seminars and 'Virginia Mediation Month', February 1994-January 1995; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - SPIDR correspondence-October 26 Board Meeting for new Executive Director and June 12 Resolution Copies, June-October, 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - SPIDR Environmental/Public Disputes Sector-University of California, Santa Cruz conference agenda, July 1-3, 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - SPIDR Strategic Planning Retreat, May 25-June 17, 1994; Record Group 2 Series 4 (Box 214, Folder 7)